为什么
还有什么好讨论的
我不喜欢他
我不在乎他认识谁
我们这批货  信得过他吗
大人物
最高统帅是吧
更像是油炸师傅...
"炸鸡男"
你要干嘛都行
但必须要有我这一票才行
永远别相信南美人
他们肮脏下流
他弄坏了我的玩具
他只是在找乐子罢了
一会儿就没事
不  我恨他  我要他死
给你老叔拿瓶啤酒好吗
不  要冰镇的
这就是你想要的
要你兄弟死  对吧
你还得加把劲
如果真想救他的话
你觉得他能撑多久
一分钟  或是更久  或是更短
家人比什么都重要
绝
命
毒
师
第三季
第七集
喂  你可没抓住我什么把柄
Hey, you got nothing on me, yo.
好吧  你可以给我律师打电话  索尔·古德曼
All right, you can call my lawyer, Saul Goodman.
去和我律师谈  懂吗
Talk to my lawyer, all right?
听到了吗  我无可奉告
Hey, you hear me. I got nothing to say.
我告诉过你  你可以给我...
I told you. You can call my--
上帝啊
Ah, Christ! God!
你还搞到了我的电话号码
You had my cell phone number!
还知道我老婆的名字
You had my wife's name!
你是怎么知道的
How'd you do it?
你和谁一伙的
Huh? Who you working with?
如果你...准备好了要谈谈
If you're, uh, ready to talk,
他们要一份书面声明
they want to get a statement.
你对这里发生的一切的解释
Your side of what happened here.
或者我们可以拖到下次再来
Or we can hold him off till another time.
你可能得和律师谈谈
Maybe you'll want to talk to a lawyer.
笑一个
There it is.
艾德里安
Yo, Adrian.
史泰龙电影《洛奇》里被打的鼻青脸肿那位
洛奇这么叫的  他想念这张脸了
Rocky called. He wants his face back.
别这样  开心一点嘛
Come on. I got to cheer you up.
看到这照片没  这就是你的刑满释放证
You see that? That's your Get Out of Jail Free card.
你知道什么叫刑满释放证  对吧
You understand Get Out of Jail Free card, right?
这机会千载难逢
I mean, just blink once if you're following.
缉毒局的噩梦
The DEA's worst nightmare
如果这张照片公之于众的话
is that face out in public.
到时候他们将对我们平克曼少爷
They're going to have to steer a wide berth
唯恐避之不及了
of young Master Pinkman
因为到时愤怒的公众就如同
for fear of the P.R. Poop storm
潮水一般势不可挡
that will rain down on them
如果这消息走漏了的话
if this story ever gets out.
我是说  你挨的这顿揍
I mean, this-- this beating?
对你来说简直是恩赐
Best thing for you.
你已经稳操胜券了
You're home free.
好事  对吧
Good, right?
对的
Right.
我的天
Oh, my God.
现在二人组里你明显比较可爱一点
You're now officially the cute one of the group.
调侃披头士乐队里保罗是吉他手 林戈是鼓手
保罗  来见见林戈  林戈 这是保罗
Paul, meet Ringo. Ringo, Paul.
这是...我...
This is-- I--
杰西  我...对此万分抱歉
Jesse, I'm-- I am so sorry for this.
本不该发展成这样的
This should not have happened.
但还是这样了
But it did.
拜你所赐
No thanks to you.
至少计划成功了
But the plan did work.
如果不把他引开  我们现在
We would have been locked up right now
已经被关起来了
if we didn't lure him away.
但这一切...
But this--
这一切...我...
this-- I just--
是我始料未及的
I never saw this coming.
所以...
So...
那现在该怎么办
What, uh... W-what happens now?
现在该怎么办
What happens now?
我来告诉你该怎么办
I'll tell you what happens now.
你那混蛋连襟玩完了
Your scumbag brother-in-law is finished,
死定了
done.
听懂了吗
You understand?
我跟他没完  我要他一辈子都欠我
I will own him when this is over.
他挣的每一分钱
Every cent he earns,
他老婆挣的每一分钱
every cent his wife earns,
都是我的
is mine.
无论他去哪里
Anyplace he goes,
无论他在哪里
anywhere he turns,
我都会跟他到死
I'm going to be there,
分一杯羹
grabbing my share.
哪怕他躲到提华纳洗厕所为生
He'll be scrubbing toilets in Tijuana for pennies,
提华纳是墨西哥西北部城市
我也会站他旁边提成的
and I'll be standing over him to get my cut.
我要他早上一醒来第一个看到的就是我
He'll see me when he wakes up in the morning
我要他晚上爬着睡
and when he crawls to sleep
因为他那狗窝
in whatever rat hole's left for him
已经被我碾得粉碎
after I shred his house down,
我他妈要化成厉鬼缠他一辈子
I will haunt his crusty ass forever
直到他自己
until the day
举枪饮弹自尽
he sticks a gun up his mouth and pulls the trigger
就为了能把我从他脑子里驱除出去
just to get me out of his head.
这就是接下来要发生的
That's what happens next.
我的建议...
Uh, my advice--
这办法听起来可不太好
that's probably not a good strategy.
他们现在怕你
I mean, they're scared of you right now.
他们根本不想与你扯上关系
They want nothing to do with you.
但如果你惹了他们
But if you hit them,
他们肯定被迫还击
they're forced to hit back hard.
他们会查个天翻地覆
I mean, they will turn over every rock
让你无处躲藏
hither, thither, and yon
直到有人说漏嘴  泄了密
until someone spills the beans on you
或是泄了与你有关的人的密
and anyone associated with you,
包括你现在的合伙人
uh, present company included.
对  我觉得索尔说的非常有道理
Yeah, I think what Saul is saying makes a lot of sense.
杰西  还是继续生活  往前看吧
Jesse, move on with your life.
别去想这一切了
Leave it behind, all of it.
一切照旧
Nothing changes.
我一离开这
Once I walk out of here,
就去搞辆新房车  继续制毒
I get myself a new RV and go start cooking again.
你凭什么认为
How exactly do you think
你能侥幸逃脱的了
you're going to get away with that?
他们会逮到你的
They will catch you.
那又怎样
So what?
什么
What?
我有刑满释放证
I have a Get Out of Jail Free card.
我可能是夸大了你...这张脸的影响力
Hey, I may have overstated the, uh, power of your face.
不行
Not this.
如果警察逮到了我
If the cops catch me...
我会告诉他们最想知道的
I give them what they want the most.
你
You.
他们逮了我
They nab me,
我就和他们做个交易  供出谁是海森堡
I make a deal to give up the great Heisenberg
还有他那百万毒品交易网络
and his million-dollar drug ring.
你就是我的自由通行证  贱人
You're my free pass, bitch.
你就那么肯定吗
You're so sure.
听着  他被汉克打的都失去意识了
Look, if he didn't give up my name
都没把我供出来
while Hank was beating him senseless,
那他就肯定不会供出来
he's never going to talk.
那你觉得刚才那是什么意思  吓唬你吗
What do you think that was in there, a bluff?
他想要搞死你的连襟
He wants your brother-in-law.
而且绝对有一大票的律师
And there's going to be a parade of lawyers
排成行的等着接这案子
creaming their Underoos for a case like that.
我是说  如果不是我有涉及
I mean, I'd take it myself
此事的话  我肯定也去接这活儿了
if it wouldn't cause so much collateral damage.
至于他说要再去制毒
And him cooking again.
不用考虑如果  他肯定被捕  当他被捕时
Hey, when, not if, he gets caught,
他面临20年监禁
and he's facing 20 years,
你觉得他会怎么做
what'll he do then?
相信我  贼之间毫无信义可言
Believe me, there's no honor among thieves.
当然  我们除外
Except for us, of course.
不  他会...
No, he'll--
他会清醒过来的
he'll come around.
万一醒不了呢
And if he doesn't,
那就得谈谈可能采取的措施了
there may come a time to talk options.
措施
Options?
我非常确信平克曼先生涉嫌
I'm convinced that Mr. Pinkman was involved
制造和分发销售
in the manufacture and distribution
苯基-2-甲基苯丙胺
of phenyl-2 methamphetamine,
我们称之为蓝色冰毒
specifically what we're calling the blue meth.
我跟踪他到废料场
I tracked him to a scrap yard
他在那藏匿了一辆80年代的野营房车
where he stored an early '80s camper,an RV.
我坚信那是一处移动实验室  专门制毒的
While waiting for a warrant to search this vehicle,
在等待车辆搜查令的时候
which I believed to be a rolling meth lab,
我接到一个电话
I received a telephone call
说我老婆玛丽出了车祸受了伤
telling me my wife Marie had been injured in an accident.
听到这个消息
Upon hearing the news,
我离开了平克曼先生和他的房车
I left Mr. Pinkman and his vehicle
去我老婆那了
to tend to my wife.
到医院以后
After arriving at the hospital,
我才发觉那个急救电话是个骗局
I learned the emergency call was a hoax.
幸运的是  我的老婆没有受伤
My wife, fortunately, was unharmed.
所以我立刻回到了废料场
So I immediately went back to the salvage yard,
但是房车已经消失了
but the RV was gone.
很有可能是被就地销毁了
Most likely destroyed on site.
而就在这时
And it was at this point
你开车去了杰西·平克曼的家
that you drove to the home of Jesse Pinkman?
我们今天先谈到这里吧
I think we're done here.
施拉德探员需要回家休息
Agent Schrader needs to get home, get some rest.
没问题
That's fine.
只是确定一下
But just to confirm,
你是在行使你的避而不答权利吗
you're taking the Fifth here?
以美国宪法第五条修正案为庇护  采取避而不答
是的  没错
Yeah. That's correct.
好的  只是想给你们提个醒
Okay. Well, we just want to give you all a heads up.
平克曼先生正在起诉此事
Mr. Pinkman is pressing charges in this matter.
他已给出
He's given a detailed version
整件事的详细经过
of events as he sees them.
毒枭之言可信吗
The word of a meth head.
我们了解他的过去
We know all about his history.
我们都非常清楚
We're well aware,
但是他的毒性测试
but toxicology on Pinkman--
结果正常  他没有吸毒
his blood is clean, he's not using.
据我们所知  他甚至拒绝服用医嘱
The kid is even refusing his doctor-ordered pain meds,
用的止痛药
as far as we can tell.
那么...
So, um...
...接下来要怎么办
...where do we go from here?
会来几个司法部的人
A couple of gentlemen from OPR will come down,
可能是明天上午
probably tomorrow morning.
詹妮斯会另外安排的
Janice will give us an exact time on that.
你的人还将继续你的调查
And you men will be continuing your investigation,
那么...
so...
谢谢配合
Thanks for your time.
好的  我们...
Right. We just--
还有一件事
We need one more thing.
施拉德探员手部的照片  需要记录在案
Photo of Agent Schrader's hands, for the record.
当然
Yes, of course.
如你愿意  请撕掉绷带
Bandage off, if you would.
把手放在桌上就好
Um, on the table is fine.
平放在桌上
Flat on the table is fine.
一切都会好起来的
It's all going to work out.
这么多年  你对他们太好了
You've been too good to them for too many years.
我想我们应该心照不宣
I hope it goes without saying
对外人绝口不提此事
that we're not talking to anybody about this, okay?
好的
Okay.
玛丽  你告诉谁了
Marie, who?
有时间吗
Do you have a minute?
当然
Sure.
犯罪的确很赚
I guess crime does pay.
你不是特地来羞辱我的吧
I don't suppose you just came by to insult me.
当然不是  我们得谈谈
No. We need to talk.
汉克的事你听说了吗
You heard about Hank?
和这个杰西·平克曼有关的
About what happened with this, um, Jesse Pinkman?
我知道
Yes, I know.
不管汉克在调查什么
Whatever Hank was investigating,
他在找一辆房车
him trying to find an RV,
有没有可能
is there any danger
最终结果指向你
that could lead back to you?
怎么可能
No. Why would it?
这就是你来的原因吗
Is this why you're here?
我是来和你谈谈汉克的
I'm here to talk about Hank.
如果平克曼控告他
You know what's going to happen to him
你知道他会怎样吗
if this Pinkman presses charges?
汉克会一无所有
Hank could lose everything.
我想或许...
I thought maybe, um...
或许你能帮他
There's a way you could help him.
怎么帮
How?
联系平克曼
Contact Pinkman.
劝他撤消控诉
Get him to drop the charges.
听着  斯凯勒  我不知道
Look, Skyler, I don't know what kind of relationship
你是如何想像我和这个人的关系
you picture me having with this person.
我不是在要求你
I'm not asking.
他曾经...现在...
He was-- He's--
他不是我的朋友
He's not my friend.
我们根本不...
I mean, it's not as if we--
-我...  -我们以前关系也不好
- I'm--  - ...were even close.
我没有强求
I'm not asking.
但你一定能和他说些什么
But there must be something you could say.
连试都不试一下吗
Isn't it even worth a try?
汉克是你的家人
Hank is your family.
目前不是了
Not currently.
你说什么
What?
我说目前不是了
I said not currently.
我上班迟到了  得走了
I'm late. I have to go.
你来了  我都开始担心了
Hello. I was starting to get worried.
车子有点问题
Car trouble.
那岂不是很郁闷
Oh. That's a bummer.
下次你应该给我电话
You should call me next time.
我去接你
I'll pick you up.
不用  今天怎么不穿凉鞋了
No, uh, no sandals today?
我想...
I just thought--
显得更专业点
a bit more professional.
一切都走上正轨了
Well, everything is on track.
蒸馏物好了  只需等到...
We got our distillate. Just waiting to--
把托盘准备好
Let's get our trays ready.
要干净的  不能沾水
Clean, no moisture.
准备好了
Done.
那么...
Is our, uh...
溶剂过滤好了吗
Our solvent filtered?
我就猜到你会问
I thought you might ask that.
过滤好了
Done.
很好
That's good.
齐心协力  亲密无间  要的就是这效果
Hand in glove. That's what we strive for.
你知道吗
You know,
这或许是一段伟大友谊的开端
this might be the beginning of a beautiful friendship.
就是你们吗
So, you the gentlemen?
算你们找对人了  我有很多宝贝
Lucky you boys called me. I got a load to pick up.
我正在运点40口径的去孟菲斯城
I'm taking the 40 straight through to Memphis.
我可以出让15把左右
I could hammer it out in about 15,
但那里有位姑娘
but there's a girl down there
叫莱妮或者罗莉  可能是弗兰
named Lainie or Lolly or something. Maybe Fran.
她有特殊的癖好
She's got one of these fetish things--
喜欢被人撒尿
wants to get peed on.
希望今晚能见到她
You know I was hoping to see her tonight,
但她真的挺按部就班的
but she is really straight about.
要10点前睡觉
Wanted to get sleep before 10:00,
所以这次交易越快越好
so I want to wrap it up here ASAP
因为路况总是未知数
because traffic can be a wild card,
好奇的观光客之类
you know, rubbernecking and such.
意外的是  这种喜欢被人撒尿的女人
The surprising thing is women who like to get peed on
总是来自气候温暖的地方
always tend to be from the warmer climates.
总以为寒冷地区的女人
You'd think the ones in the colder zones
更可能有这种倾向
would be more inclined.
如果人体不能适应新环境
Maybe it's a shock to the system
也许会休克
if the body's not properly acclimated,
还是把这个问题留给聪明人去想吧
but, you know, I leave that for smart minds than me.
科学本身就是一个谜
Science is a mystery.
来瞅瞅
Well, take a gander.
价钱好商量
Prices are negotiable.
大批量购买有折扣
Buying in bulk gets you a discount.
这些小宝贝有特别优惠
I'm running a special on these little honeys.
空尖型子弹
JHPs. Hollow-point bullets,
当地人都把这些宝贝称作黑死病
known by the natives as Black Death.
看看吧  中意吗
Check it out. Huh. You like that?
太棒了  你会爱死它的
So sweet, you want to lick it.
镀镍铜锌合金外壳  黑拉巴洛克斯弹头
Nickel-plated brass casing, Lubalox coat for panache.
弹头六片利爪受到挤压会立马展开
Sucker has six razor claws that expand upon impact.
可以把你妈的脑袋撕个大洞
Shred your mama's head like a cabbage.
拿着吧  免费
Keep it. On the house?
我废话说太多了
Anyhow, I've been windjamming long enough.
何不告诉我你们要买什么
Why don't you boys tell me what you're looking for?
你们想要什么  需要什么
What is you want? What is you need?
有什么可以效劳的
What can I do you for?
防弹衣
Vests.
防弹衣  当然  有的是
Vests? Hell, yeah, we got vests.
就在这里
Right here.
光滑舒适
Sleek, comfortable,
热粘合非交织凯夫拉尔纤维
thermally bonded non-interwoven Kevlar fiber.
阻挡子弹就像对着修女手淫一样舒服
Stop a bullet like a soft wank against a Quaker girl.
子弹就是穿不透
Just ain't getting through.
轻吗
And lightweight?
太他妈轻了
Damn, so lightweight,
你根本感觉不到穿了它
you'll forget you're wearing it.
有用吗
They work?
屁话  当然有用
Sure as shit, they do.
没有它我绝不出门
I don't leave home without it.
你他妈
What the hell?
你他妈把我肋骨弄断了  你个混蛋
You broke my freakin' rib, you maniac son of a bitch.
不客气
You're welcome!
你设的几度
What temperature did you set here?
那里吗  是...
There? That's...
5号机  75摄氏度
Station Five-- 75 C.
我说过85度
I said 85.
8-5
8-5.
我...我写下来的
I, uh-- I wrote it down.
你说是75度
You said 75.
我写了
I-- I wrote it.
那就是你记错了
Well, then you wrote it wrong.
那不是我说的  我说85度
That's not what I said. I said 85.
一直是85度
It's always been 85--
不是75  也不是95
not 75, not 95.
85  度
85.
这是化学  温度是关键
This is chemistry. Degrees matter.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm very sorry.
很好  你感到抱歉
Great. You're sorry.
同时你酿造了50加仑的无用烂泥
Meanwhile, you've just brewed 50 gallons of useless sludge.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
倒掉  统统倒掉
Just dump it. Dump it all.
这一批都毁了
This batch is ruined.
你看上去挺帅
You look nice.
我像电视上那种天气预报员
I look like a TV weatherman.
来杯咖啡吗
You want a coffee?
我榨了些橙汁
I squeezed some orange juice.
要来一杯吗
You want to glass of orange juice?
不用了
I'm all right.
你打算怎么对他们说
What are you going to tell them?
你要这样告诉他们
Here's what you're going to tell them.
是他先攻击你的
He attacked you.
他先打我
He attacked me?
他操家伙打你
He-- he swung at you with something.
他...
He-- he--
-打我  -他用管子打你
- swung at me. - ... attacked you with a pipe.
管子
With a pipe?
一切发生的太快
It happened fast.
他拒捕
He resisted arrest,
你肌肉记忆本能反应
and muscle memory kicked in,
所以你被迫解除他的武装
and you had to disarm him.
肌肉记忆
Muscle memory.
是的  这种事经常发生
Yes. It happens all the time.
经过多年的训练
Years of training,
你的身体不假思索地做出反应
and your body acted faster than your brain.
你除了打他没别的选择
You had no choice but to hit him.
-你只有反击  -玛丽  玛丽  玛丽
- You had to fight back. - Marie, Marie, Marie.
不
No.
我不打算去撒谎
I'm not going to go in there and lie.
这是你和社会渣滓
It's some lowlife degenerate
之间的较量
versus you...
你只是在履行自己的职责
Doing the job you're supposed to.
为什么你行得端做得正
Why should you be the one who pays
反而要付出代价
for doing the right thing?
亲爱的  我做的不对
Oh, baby, it wasn't the right thing.
我的职责不是这个
It's not what the job is.
我应该比这做得更好
I'm supposed to be better than that.
现在你只犯了一个错
And you made one mistake.
不  不只是一个错  我一直
No, it wasn't one mistake. I've been--
我一直以来都
I've been...
处在崩溃的边缘  你明白吗
...unraveling, you know?
我晚上再也不能安睡
I don't sleep at night anymore.
我战栗
I freeze.
全身僵硬
I freeze up.
我的胸口发闷  无法呼吸
My chest gets all tight. I-- I can't breathe.
就是...
Just--
我恐惧不已
I panic.
自从塞拉曼加那件事开始就这样
Ever since that Salamanca thing.
屠库·塞拉曼加
I mean, Tuco Salamanca.
那个罪该万死的人渣
If ever a scumbag deserved a bullet between the eyes.
那件事改变了我
It changed me.
我好像控制不住自己了
And I can't seem to control it.
我努力反抗
I tried to fight it.
但后来又有埃尔帕索的事
But then El Paso.
可情况只是越来越糟糕
And it's just gotten worse.
我对平克曼做出的事
What I did to Pinkman...
我不应该是那个样子
...that's not who I'm supposed to be.
那不是我
That's not me.
所有这些
All this--
所发生的这一切  我...
everything that's happened, I--
我可以向上帝发誓  玛丽
I swear to God, Marie,
我觉得像是冥冥之中  要告诉我什么
I think the universe is trying to tell me something,
现在我终于
and I'm finally...
准备好要听了
Ready to listen.
我再也不是曾经的我了
I'm just not the man I thought I was.
我想我的警察生涯到头了
I think I'm done as a cop.
作出这个决定并不容易
Now, this is-- is not an easy decision,
但是这是我必须作出的决定
but it is one that I have to make.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
现在这个
This whole...
对于盖尔的情况
Gale situation--
他就是不行
he's-- he's just not working out.
是的  现在
Yes. Now.
听起来也许有点奇怪
It-- It may sound unorthodox,
但我认为
but I think
我们的首选  最好的人选
our first-- best option...
是杰西·平克曼
Is Jesse Pinkman.
喂
Hello?
这
It--
不  听我说
No, look. Th-There's--
我们之间有种默契
There's a-- a shorthand that exists between us--
有共同的经历
experience together
说实话  这种默契的程度
at a level that, quite frankly,
我和盖尔之间永远不可能达到
I-- I'm just never going to reach with Gale.
听着  福林先生
Look, Mr. Fring,
我接受你的邀请时
when I accepted your offer,
说好实验室归我管
I was told the lab is mine.
我也最清楚该怎么管理它
And I know best how to run it.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢  是的  我会的  我会的
Thank you. Yes, I will. I will.
好的  再见
Okay. Good-bye.
听着  有事情告诉你
Listen, something's come up.
我想是一次好机会
And, uh, I think it's a good opportunity.
有个职位空缺
There's been a job opening.
我需要个新的实验助手
I need a new lab assistant.
我已经为你干过了
I already did my time.
你干吗不去给你自己找只猴子
Why don't you just go get yourself a monkey?
我不要猴子  我要你
I don't want a monkey. I want you.
噢  老天  谢谢
Oh, gee, thanks.
没兴趣
Well, not interested.
我自己有事情做
I got my own thing going on.
想救你的蠢货连襟没门儿
Nice try saving your ass head brother-in-law.
我不是为这个而来  杰西
That's not why I'm here, Jesse.
还有别的事
There's more.
你将不仅仅是我的助手
It's more than an assistant.
也是合作伙伴
Partners.
我们又要成为搭档了
We'll be partners again.
一切照旧  五五分成
Split everything 50-50, just like before.
一人得一百五十万
$1.5 million each.
不
No.
我想你没听明白
I don't think you heard--
我听得很清楚
I've heard you fine.
我说不
I said no.
让我理一下思路
Let me understand this.
你这是在拒绝一百五十万
You're turning down $1 1/2 million.
我不是在拒绝钱
I am not turning down the money.
我在拒绝你
I am turning down you.
你明白吗
You get it?
我不想和你有任何瓜葛
I want nothing to do with you.
自从我遇见你
Ever since I met you,
我所关心的一切
everything I have ever cared about
全都没了
is gone...
毁了  废了  死了
Ruined, turned to shit, dead,
自从我和你--伟大的海森堡搅合在一起之后
ever since I hooked up with the great Heisenberg.
我感到空前的孤独
I have never been more alone.
我变得一无所有
I have nothing!
没人理我
No one!
懂了吗  什么都没了
All right? It's all gone!
懂吗
Get it?
不  不  不
No. No, no.
你怎么会
Why--
你怎么会懂
Why would you get it?
你只要得到你想要的
What do you even care
你还关心什么
as long as you get what you want?
我说对了吧
Right?
你他妈根本就没在乎过我
You don't give a shit about me.
你说我没用
You said I was no good.
一无是处
I'm nothing!
现在怎么又要我了
Why would you want me? Huh?
你说过我的毒是下等货
You said my meth is inferior, right?
不是吗
Right?
嘿  是你说我制的毒是垃圾
Hey! You said my cook was garbage!
去你妈的  老头  去你的
Hey, screw you, man! Screw you!
你制的冰毒很好  杰西
Your meth is good, Jesse.
不比我的差
As good as mine.
是我
Yeah.
五五分
50-50.
是的  五五分
Yes. 50-50.
好吧
Okay.
合作伙伴
Partners.
太好了
Good.
通用痛苦程度评估表
这就是你想做的书面声明吗
This is the statement you want to give?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
汉克  你不必这么做
Hank, you don't have to do this.
不  我...
No, I--
我要这样
I do.
我没事
I'm good.
那我们姑且认为
So we understand
如果我们这样写  你会签字
if we write it up like that, you'll sign it.
事情就是那样的
That's the way it happened.
我愿意承担后果
I accept the consequences.
介于上述事实
In the light of these facts...
从即刻起  你被停薪停职
As of this moment, you're suspended without pay.
请交出警徽和佩枪
I have to ask you to hand over your badge and your gun.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
施拉德
Schrader.
等一会
Hold up.
什么事  长官
Yes, sir?
我想告诉你件事
I just want to tell you something.
但说清楚  你不是从我这儿听来的
And to be clear, you didn't hear it from me.
我不想你空欢喜一场
I don't want you to get your hopes up,
不过上面传下话来
but the word in the pipeline is
平克曼撤诉了
Pinkman isn't pressing charges.
为什么
Why not?
谁知道呢
Who the hell knows?
也许你有个守护天使呢
Maybe you have a guardian angel.
事情有了好转
It went fine.
好转的意思...
Well, fine means what--
就是好转的意思  对
means what it means. Yeah.
我会
I'll, uh...
等我到家了我会全部告诉你  好吗
I'll tell you all about it when I get home, okay?
是的
Yeah. It's--
是的  就是
Yeah, it's just--
我也不知道  亲爱的  我就是觉得
I don't know, baby. I just think--
我想我们可能没事了
I think we may be okay.
是的
Yeah.
好  我也爱你
Okay. I love you, too.
施拉德
Schrader.
你仔细听好
I need you to listen very carefully.
有两个人要来杀你
Two men are coming to kill you.
再说一遍
Come again?
他们正向你的车子走去
They're approaching your car.
你有一分钟时间逃走
You have one minute.
不知道你玩什么把戏  滚一边去吧
I don't get the gag, jerk off.
他们就要来了
They're coming.
喂
Hello.
嘿  听...
Hey, Li--
嘿  格米  我是汉克
Hey, Gomie, this is Hank.
不知道你这通电话什么意思
I don't know what that call's supposed to be,
即使按你的水准也太白痴了
but it's dumb even by your standards,
听到留言给我回电话
so call me when you get this.
干掉他
不
No.
这样便宜你了